let questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",
    options: [
      "A.Pablo Picasso",
      "B.Salvador Dali",
      "C.Vincent van Gogh",
      "D.Henri Matisse",
    ],
    answer: "B.Salvador Dali",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",
    options: ["A.Impressionism", "B.Expressionism", "C.Futurism", "D.Cubism"],
    answer: "D.Cubism",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",
    options: [
      "A.Pablo Picasso",
      "B.Salvador Dali",
      "C.Vincent van Gogh",
      "D.Henri Matisse",
    ],
    answer: "B.Salvador Dali",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",
    options: [
      "A.Vincent van Gogh",
      "B.Salvador Dali",
      "C.Edvard Munch",
      "D.Claude Monet",
    ],
    answer: "C.Edvard Munch",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",
    options: ["A.Impressionism", "B.Expressionism", "C.Fauvism", "D.Cubism"],
    answer: "C.Fauvism",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",
    options: [
      "A.Impressionism",
      "B.Futurism",
      "C.Surrealism",
      "D.Abstract Expressionism",
    ],
    answer: "B.Futurism",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",
    options: [
      "A.Claude Monet",
      "B.Paul Cezanne",
      "C.Paul Gauguin",
      "D.Paul Klee",
    ],
    answer: "A.Claude Monet",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",
    options: [
      "A.Henri Matisse",
      "B.Vincent van Gogh",
      "C.Salvador Dali",
      "D.Pablo Picasso",
    ],
    answer: "D.Pablo Picasso",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",
    options: [
      "A.Claude Mone",
      "B.Paul Cezanne",
      "C.Pablo Picasso",
      "D.Vincent van Gogh",
    ],
    answer: "C.Pablo Picasso",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",
    options: [
      "A.Auguste Rodin",
      "B.Alexander Calder",
      "C.Jean Arp",
      "D.Henry Moore",
    ],
    answer: "A.Auguste Rodin",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
];
